

Daniel Batanov

Experienced professional with a diverse background in Enineering, Architecture, and QA. Two years ago, I discovered a passion for building user-friendly applications that drive business growth and enhance user experience. Since then, I have worked my skills up through courses, projects, and internships. Now I am excited to make a difference with technology.

PROJECTS

Ra-auth-ui open source npm released npm | Git Out of the box authentication layouts, hooks and pipelines to integrate into react-admin

Book Store (full-stack) (Stripe) Live | Demo | Git An e-commerce book store with an admin panel, Stipe payments and more

Mini Finance Softuniada 2024 Live | Demo | Git A finance web app, offering virtual cards, top-ups, contacts, transactions and history

Ai Builder (full-stack OpenAI) Live | Demo | Git An ai webpage builder that generates code and display webpages based on user prompts

SKILLS

Tech skills

JavaScript ES6+ | HTML5 | CSS | SASS | Tailwind React | Typescript | Angular NodeJS | Express | Handlebars Chai | Mocha | Playwright | Jest MongoDB | Mongoose | MySQL Git | NPM | Yarn | HTTP | REST | AJAX

Soft skills

Growth mindset | (Motivation Problem-solving (Communication)(Teamwork)(Time management

CERTIFICATES / ACHIEVEMENTS

- Front-End Developer Diploma at SoftUni
- Softuniada Programming Olympiad Top 10

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

SoftUni | Web development UAECG | Master of Architecture High School of Mathematics | IT

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer Intern

Focus on backend development

Dec 2024 - now

- Cost-Effective Solutions
- Building a scraper software for NGO organization
- · Working in a team of 8 individuals
- Internship period fixed at 3 months
- Using technologies like Node, Typescript postgreSQL, Tailwind, Prisma, React, Git and more

Front-end Developer Intern

(Mar - Dec 2024)

Humble Software Ltd

- · Worked closely with a senior tech lead
- Building internal libraries based on React Admin using React, Typescript, Material U, Git and more

Architect

2021 - 2023

IPA architecture and more

Intern Architect

2018 - 2019

Design Art "K&K"

2017 - 2018

Intern Architect Integra Consult Project

2014 - 2015

Manual Quality Assurance Gameloft

- Developed over 100 unique test cases
- · Assisted with resolving major issues during overtime

LANGUAGES

English Proficient



Bulgarian Native

